canon.co.in 2015-12-07

# Privacy policy - Canon India - Personal

###  Acceptance

This website ("Canon Website") is provided to you by Canon Singapore Pte. Ltd.("Canon") on the following terms and conditions ("Terms and Conditions"). By accessing any page on this Canon Website, you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions. These Terms and Conditions may be updated by Canon from time to time without prior notice. You should check the Terms and Conditions for updates each time you access the Canon Website.

Top

###  Our Commitment To Privacy

As your privacy is important to us, we provide this Statement explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. For easy accessibility, this Statement will be made available on our homepage and on every page of our website.  

Top

### Scope

This Statement covers all aspects of Canon Website on which our privacy statement hyperlink appears. The information covered by this Statement is personal information an individual provides to Canon outside of his/her trade, business or profession ("Information").

Top

### The Information We Collect

There are two forms of Information that Canon collects online: Website Visitorship Information and Personal Identifiable Information voluntarily provided to Canon by Canon Website visitors.

**Website Visitorship Information**  
Canon gathers Information on Website activity, such as data on the number of people who visit the Canon Website, the pages they visit, the duration of their stay, etc. Website Visitorship Information is: 

  * Collected on an aggregate, anonymous basis, which means no Personal Identifiable Information is associated with this data; 
  * Gathered through the use of web server logs and cookies. 

**Personal Identifiable Information**  
Personal Identifiable Information is collected on certain pages of the Canon Website. If you contact Canon online to ask a question, post a feedback, register a recently-purchased product, inquire about products you may already own, or participate in voluntary online surveys, you will find that those contact forms ask for certain types of Personal Identifiable Information to assist us in complying with your requests. 

  * Canon may ask you to provide Personal Identifiable Information, on specific pages of the Canon Website. The information requested may include your name, address, e-mail address, contact number, product model and serial numbers and the dates of purchase, and your comments. Personal Identifiable Information may be forwarded to a Canon business unit or the appropriate Canon headquarters, subsidiary or affiliate company that is equipped to handle your inquiry or feedback.

Personal Identifiable Information is collected only when Canon Website visitors voluntarily provide it and such information is not necessary to simply browse the Canon Website.

Top

### How We Use Information

We use the Information you provide about yourself to perform the service you have requested and may use that Information to provide you with information about other Canon products and promotions that may be of interest to you. Your Information may be shared among our employees, agents or other related and unrelated Canon entities and/or business partners acting on our behalf to conduct surveys or to provide a product or service you have requested. We do not share this information with non-Canon companies except to the extent necessary to complete your requests and, in the event we do share it, it is subject to their agreement to treat it as confidential business information and with the understanding that it may not be used for any purpose other than to perform their function. If you inquire about a product that Canon does not sell directly, we may forward your information to a Canon authorized dealer, distributor or other reseller. Use of your information by the authorized dealer, distributor or reseller is governed by its own policies, not Canon's. Canon may also provide links to dealer sites from the Canon Website. See our discussion below and in our Terms of Use about further information about such links.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive as well as to provide you with product and service updates, special promotions and offers.

In the course of growing or restructuring our business, we may purchase the assets of another company or sell the assets of our company. During these transactions, information about customers is frequently considered a business asset that is the subject of such a purchase or sale. Also, in the unlikely event that Canon, or substantially all of its assets are either acquired or subject to liquidation in bankruptcy, Information may be transferred as well.

The Canon Website may contain hyperlinks to and from other Internet websites, including other Canon Company websites. These websites may have different privacy practices from the ones described here. Since this Statement applies solely to this Website, please read the privacy statements of the other websites you visit. For more information about hyperlinks, please see the Terms of Use posted elsewhere on our Canon Website.

Terms of Useand other agreements, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Canon, Canon Website users or others. This includes exchanging Information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

Top

### Our Commitment To Data Security

Canon strives to ensure that our systems are secure and that they meet industry standards. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the Information we collect online. The security of personal information you may submit in connection with a promotion entry, survey response, and/or registration for any feature on the Canon Website is of the utmost concern to us, and we strive to ensure its security on our systems. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk. We will continue to assess new technology to evaluate its ability to provide additional protection of your Information.

Top

### Right to Amend our Website Privacy Statement

Canon reserves the right to amend this Statement at any time. Changes will be effective immediately upon posting on the Website.

Top

### How To Contact Us

If you have questions or concerns about this Statement, please contact us at:

Canon Singapore Pte. Ltd.  
1 HarbourFront Avenue #04-01,   
Keppel Bay Tower   
Singapore 098632  
Tel: (65) 6799 8888   
Fax: (65) 6799 8882 

Top
